- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_01_Talk_Quam_Varang
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_01_SearchRing_Talk_Quam_Varang_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_01_SearchRing_Talk_Quam_Varang_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_01_Talk_Mordred_Haughty
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_01_SearchRing_Talk_Mordred_Haughty_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_01_SearchRing_Talk_Mordred_Haughty_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_01_Talk_Morgaine_Cabin
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_01_SearchRing_Talk_Morgaine_Cabin_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_01_SearchRing_Talk_Morgaine_Cabin_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_02_Talk_Daichi_Enenra
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_02_GetDaichi_Talk_Daichi_Enenra_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_02_GetDaichi_Talk_Daichi_Enenra_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_02_Talk_Daichi_sealed
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_02_GetDaichi_Talk_Daichi_sealed_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_02_GetDaichi_Talk_Daichi_sealed_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_02_Talk_Daichi_fight
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_02_GetDaichi_Talk_Daichi_fight_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_02_GetDaichi_Talk_Daichi_fight_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_02_Talk_Daichi_onboarded
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_02_GetDaichi_Talk_Daichi_onboarded_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_02_GetDaichi_Talk_Daichi_onboarded_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_05_Talk_Zander_RuneForge
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_05_RetrieveRune_Talk_Zander_RuneForge_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_05_RetrieveRune_Complete_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_03_Talk_Daichi_GiveCharm
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_03_EnterCastle_Talk_Daichi_GiveCharm_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_03_EnterCastle_Talk_Daichi_GiveCharm_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_03_Talk_Morgaine_IceResearch
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_03_EnterCastle_Talk_Morgaine_IceResearch_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_03_EnterCastle_Talk_Morgaine_IceResearch_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_04_Talk_Mordred_CantStopMe
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Talk_Mordred_CantStopMe_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Talk_Mordred_CantStopMe_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_06_Talk_Daichi_JournalRunes
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_06_StopDevice_Talk_Daichi_JournalRunes_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_06_StopDevice_Talk_Daichi_JournalRunes_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_06_Talk_Daichi_HelpFallsDoor
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_06_StopDevice_Talk_Daichi_HelpFallsDoor_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_06_StopDevice_Talk_Daichi_HelpFallsDoor_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_07_Talk_Daichi_DefeatedMordred
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_07_WrapFrost_Talk_Daichi_DefeatedMordred_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_07_WrapFrost_Talk_Daichi_DefeatedMordred_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_07_Talk_Morgaine_MordredFrozen
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_07_WrapFrost_Talk_Morgaine_MordredFrozen_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_07_WrapFrost_Talk_Morgaine_MordredFrozen_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_02_Talk_Rima_Candidates
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_02_GetDaichi_Talk_Rima_Candidates_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_02_GetDaichi_Talk_Rima_Candidates_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_04_Talk_Rima_ScholarER
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Talk_Rima_ScholarER_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Talk_Rima_ScholarER_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_04_Talk_Rima_ArtoriusVLN
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Talk_Rima_ArtoriusVLN_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Talk_Rima_ArtoriusVLN_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_04_Talk_Rima_CantGetThrough
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Talk_Rima_CantGetThrough_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Talk_Rima_CantGetThrough_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_04_Talk_Rima_MordredNotWork
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Talk_Rima_MordredNotWork_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Talk_Rima_MordredNotWork_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_06_Talk_Rima_LizardPuzzle
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_06_StopDevice_Talk_Rima_LizardPuzzle_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_06_StopDevice_Talk_Rima_LizardPuzzle_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_06_Talk_Rima_DefeatedMordred
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_06_StopDevice_Talk_Rima_DefeatedMordred_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_06_StopDevice_Talk_Rima_DefeatedMordred_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_01_Talk_Skye_Varangians
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_01_SearchRing_Talk_Skye_Varangians_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_01_SearchRing_Talk_Skye_Varangians_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_01_Talk_Skye_Varangians_dnm
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_01_SearchRing_Talk_Skye_Varangians_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_01_SearchRing_Talk_Skye_Varangians_response_dnm_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_01_Talk_Skye_Mordred
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_01_SearchRing_Talk_Skye_Mordred_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_01_SearchRing_Talk_Skye_Mordred_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_01_Talk_Skye_AfterCaves
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_01_SearchRing_Talk_Skye_AfterCaves_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_01_SearchRing_Talk_Skye_AfterCaves_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_01_Talk_Skye_NeedFire
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_01_SearchRing_Talk_Skye_NeedFire_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_01_SearchRing_Talk_Skye_NeedFire_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_03_Talk_Skye_EscortPrisoners
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_03_EnterCastle_Talk_Skye_EscortPrisoners_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_03_EnterCastle_Talk_Skye_EscortPrisoners_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_04_Talk_Skye_StayOutside
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Talk_Skye_StayOutside_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Talk_Skye_StayOutside_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_07_Talk_Skye_DefeatedMordred
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_07_WrapFrost_Talk_Skye_DefeatedMordred_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_07_WrapFrost_Talk_Skye_DefeatedMordred_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_07_Talk_Skye_FinishQuest
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_07_WrapFrost_Talk_Skye_FinishQuest_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_07_WrapFrost_Talk_Skye_FinishQuest_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_04_Talk_Skye_MordredHasStaff
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Talk_Skye_MordredHasStaff_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Talk_Skye_MordredHasStaff_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_02_Talk_Zander_HowDaichi
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_02_GetDaichi_Talk_Zander_HowDaichi_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_02_GetDaichi_Talk_Zander_HowDaichi_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_03_Talk_Zander_HowChessboard
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_03_EnterCastle_Talk_Zander_HowChessboard_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_03_EnterCastle_Talk_Zander_HowChessboard_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_07_Talk_Grace_FinishQuest
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_07_WrapFrost_Talk_Grace_FinishQuest_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_07_WrapFrost_Talk_Grace_FinishQuest_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_04_Talk_Scholar_ArtoriusMordred
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Talk_Scholar_ArtoriusMordred_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Talk_Scholar_ArtoriusMordred_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_04_Talk_MagicDoor_FirstTry
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Talk_MagicDoor_FirstTry_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Talk_MagicDoor_FirstTry_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_04_Talk_MagicDoor_Unlock
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Talk_MagicDoor_Unlock_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Talk_MagicDoor_Unlock_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_04_Talk_Dog_CrumblyWall
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Talk_Dog_CrumblyWall_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_04_FightMage_Talk_Dog_CrumblyWall_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_06_Talk_Dog_StayGuard
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_06_StopDevice_Talk_Dog_StayGuard_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_06_StopDevice_Talk_Dog_StayGuard_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: Topic_95_s04_06_Talk_Dog_DefeatedMordred
  PlayerPrompt: "@95_s04_06_StopDevice_Talk_Dog_DefeatedMordred_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@95_s04_06_StopDevice_Talk_Dog_DefeatedMordred_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
